Let the glory of the Lord
forever be our joy
may redemption be
the theme of our song
For by grace we have been saved
and by grace we shall proclaim
to the corners of the earth
that Christ is come
Let the nations be glad
let the people rejoice
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the whole earth be filled
with the praises of the Lord
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the nations be glad
Through the ages gone before
Through the trial and the sword
Many saints and martyrs
conquered though they died
Still we're holding out the cross
Crossing ocean suffering loss
Shall endure all things to win
the crown of life
Let the nations be glad
let the people rejoice
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the whole earth be filled
with the praises of the Lord
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the nations be glad
As your holy church goes forth
in the Holy Spirit’s power
With the glories of the Gospel to explain
Now we pray Your kingdom come
And we pray Your will be done
For the honor and the glory of Your name
Let the nations be glad
let the people rejoice
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the whole earth be filled
with the praises of the Lord
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the nations be glad
let the people rejoice
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the whole earth be filled
with the praises of the Lord
For salvation belongs to our God
Let the nations be glad