Lord, I come
I confess
Bowing here
I find my rest
And without you
I fall apart
You're the one
That guides my heart
Lord, I need You, oh, I need You
Every hour I need You
My one defense, my righteousness
Oh God, how I need You
Where sin runs deep
Your grace is more
Where grace is found
is where You are
Where You are, Lord, I am free
Holiness is Christ in me
Lord, I need You, oh, I need You
Every hour I need You
My one defense, my righteousness
Oh God, how I need You
So teach my song to rise to You
When temptation comes my way
When I cannot stand I'll fall on You
Jesus, You're my hope and stay
Lord, I need You, oh, I need You
Every hour I need You
My one defense, my righteousness
Oh God, how I need You
Lord, I need You, oh, I need You
Every hour I need You
My one defense, my righteousness
Oh God, how I need You