My heart burst at its banks
Spilling with beauty and goodness
I pour it out as a song to my King
Shaping the rivers into words
What grace pours from your lips
The sound calls the
midnight to morning
The melody turns
my winter to spring
I echo it now in my worship
Ten thousand strong
You're the fairest of all
Fairest in heaven and earth
Of the children of men
You're the fairest of them
Fairest in heaven and earth
Your heart burst at the seams
Flowing with blood and with water
A song of love
pouring out from the tree singing
For the joy set before me
Ten thousand strong
You're the fairest of all
Fairest in heaven and earth
Of the children of men
You're the fairest of them
Fairest in heaven and earth
You ransomed Your bride
On the day that You died
Ascended to heaven in glory
She stands clothed in white
With her head lifted high singing
"Come and return in Your glory"
You ransomed Your bride
On the day that You died
Ascended to heaven in glory
We stand clothed in white
With her head lifted high singing
"Come and return in Your glory"
Ten thousand strong
You're the fairest of all
Fairest in heaven and earth
Of the children of men
You're the fairest of them
Fairest in heaven and earth