Oh to be, empty and lowly
Meek and unnoticed, and unknown
And to God, a vessel holy
Filled with Christ, and Christ alone
How great is God! His grandeur endless
How frail I come, before His throne
I am lost, in love relentless
That Christ be all, and I His own
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope: Not I, but Christ in me
I am poor, and I have nothing
All my deeds cannot avail
But Christ endured the Father's crushing
He bowed His head, as Mercy bled,
peace to prevail
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope: Not I, but Christ in me
Bring me low, my heart lower still
That Your grace my pride relieves
May these words resound loud until
Every tribe and tongue believes
Bring me low, my heart lower still
That Your grace my pride relieves
May these words resound loud until
Every tribe and tongue can sing
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope: Not I, but Christ in me
On golden shores of sure salvation
I will run to meet my King
Freed from shame and all accusation
He'll give Himself, nothing I'll bring
We won't fear the battle,
we won’t fear the night
We will walk the valley
with You by our side
You will go before us,
You will lead the way
We have found a refuge,
only You can save
Sing with joy now: our God is for us
The Father's love is a
strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now,
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us
Even when I stumble,
even when I fall
Even when I turn back,
still Your love is sure
You will not abandon,
You will not forsake
You will cheer me onward
with never-ending grace
Sing with joy now: our God is for us
The Father's love
is a strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now,
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us
Neither height nor depth
can separate us
Hell and death will not defeat us
He who gave His son to free us
Holds me in His love
Neither height nor depth
can separate us
Hell and death will not defeat us
He who gave His son to free us
Holds me in His love
Sing with joy now: our God is for us
The Father’s love is a
strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now,
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us
Sing with joy now: our God is for us
The Father's love is a
strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now,
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us