I'm alive
because You're alive
I am free
'cause You set me free
I'm alive, I'm alive in You, Jesus
I am Yours
'cause You said it's so
I am loved
and You won't let go
I'm alive, I'm alive in You, Jesus
O Spirit come
set our hearts with holy fire
This hope we have
our God's not dead He is alive
And He is Jesus
Nothing and no one can stop Him
There's nothing's
as strong as our God is
Our God is alive
Hey death
where is your sting?
No sin
has claim on me
I'm alive, I'm alive in You, Jesus
Oh, there's no grave
that could hold my King
'Cause He Stands
in victory
He's alive, He's alive in me, Jesus
Oh, You're alive
You're alive in me, Jesus
And He is Jesus
nothing and no one can stop Him
There's nothing
as strong as our God is
Our God is alive
And He is risen
Now we are walking in freedom
There's nothing
as strong as our Jesus
Our God is alive
So let praise rise
high in this place
For our King
stands over the grave
So let praise rise
high in this place
For our King
stands over the grave
O let praise rise
high in this place
For our King
stands over the grave
O let praise rise
high in this place
For our King
stands over the grave
And He is Jesus
nothing and no one can stop Him
There's nothing
as strong as our God is
Our God is alive
And He is risen
Now we are walking in freedom
There's nothing
as strong as our Jesus
Our God is alive
O let praise rise
high in this place
For our King
stands over the grave