Turn your eyes
upon Jesus
Look full in
His wonderful face
And the things of earth
will grow strangely dim
In the light of
His glory and grace
Turn your eyes
to the hillside
Where justice and
mercy embraced
There the Son of God
gave His life for us
And our measureless
debt was erased
Jesus, to You
we lift our eyes
Jesus, our glory
and our prize
We adore You, behold You
our Savior ever true
Oh Jesus, we turn our eyes
to You
Turn your eyes
to the morning
And see Christ
the Lion awake
What a glorious dawn
fear of death is gone
For we carry
His life in our veins
Jesus, to You
we lift our eyes
Jesus, our glory
and our prize
We adore You, behold You
our Savior ever true
Oh Jesus, we turn our eyes
to You
Turn your eyes
to the heavens
Our King will
return for His own
Every knee will bow
every tongue will shout
'All glory to Jesus alone!'
Jesus, to You
we lift our eyes
Jesus, our glory
and our prize
We adore You, behold You
our Savior ever true
Oh Jesus, we turn our eyes
to You
Jesus, to You
we lift our eyes
Jesus, our glory
and our prize
We adore You, behold You
our Savior ever true
Oh Jesus, we turn our eyes
to You
Oh Jesus,
We turn out eyes to you