From the darkness, I called Your name
Into darkness, Your mercy came
You called me out, lifted me up
How great is Your love
You bore my weakness, You took my shame
Buried my burdens in fields of grace
You called me out, lifted me up
How great is Your love
From the heights of heaven
You stepped down to earth
Innocent perfection
Gave Your life for us
We are amazed
We stand in awe
For we have been changed
By the power of the cross
How great, how great, how great is Your love
For us
In Your kindness, You lead me home
In Your presence, where I belong
You called me out, lifted me up
How great is Your love
From the heights of heaven
You stepped down to earth
Innocent perfection
Gave Your life for us
We are amazed
We stand in awe
For we have been changed
By the power of the cross
How great, how great, how great is Your love
For us
How great is Your love for us
There has never been, there will never be
A God like You, a love so true
How great, how great, how great is Your love
For us
How great is Your love for us
How great, how great, how great is Your love
For us
How great is Your love for us