We won't fear the battle
we won’t fear the night
We will walk the valley
with You by our side
You will go before us
You will lead the way
We have found a refuge
only You can save
Sing with joy now
our God is for us
The Father's love
is a strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us
Even when I stumble
even when I fall
Even when I turn back
still Your love is sure
You will not abandon
You will not forsake
You will cheer me onward
with never-ending grace
Sing with joy now
our God is for us
The Father's love
is a strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us
Neither height nor depth
can separate us
Hell and death
will not defeat us
He who gave
His son to free us
Holds me in His love
Neither height nor depth
can separate us
Hell and death
will not defeat us
He who gave
His son to free us
Holds me in His love
Sing with joy now
our God is for us
The Father's love
is a strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us
Sing with joy now
our God is for us
The Father's love
is a strong and mighty fortress
Raise your voice now
no love is greater
Who can stand against us
if our God is for us