How I love the voice of Jesus
On the cross of Calvary
He declares His work is finished
He has spoken this hope to me
Though the sun had ceased its shining
Though the war appeared as lost
Christ had triumphed over evil
It was finished upon that cross
Now the curse, it has been broken
Jesus paid the price for me
Full, the pardon he has offered
Great, the welcome that I receive
Boldly, I approach my Father
Clothed in Jesus' righteousness
There is no more guilt to carry
It was finished upon that cross
Death was once my great opponent
Fear once had a hold on me
But the Son who died to save us
Rose that we would be free indeed!
Death was once my great opponent
Fear once had a hold on me
But the Son who died to save us
Rose that we would be free indeed!
Yes, He rose that we would be free indeed!
Free from every plan of darkness
Free to live and free to love
Death is dead and Christ is risen!
It was finished upon that cross
Onward to eternal glory
To my Saviour and my God
I rejoice in Jesus' victory
It was finished upon that cross