Bless the Lord, O my soul
O my soul, worship His holy name
Sing like never before O my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
The sun comes up
It's a new day dawning
It's time to sing Your song again
Whatever may pass
And whatever lies before me
Let me be singing
When the evening comes
Bless the Lord, O my soul
O my soul, worship His holy name
Sing like never before O my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
You're rich in love
And You're slow to anger
Your name is great
And Your heart is kind
For all Your goodness
I will keep on singing
Ten thousand reasons
For my heart to find
So bless the Lord, O my soul
O my soul, worship His holy name
Sing like never before, O my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
And on that day
When my strength is failing
The end draws near
And my time has come
Still my soul will sing
Your praise unending
Ten thousand years
And then forevermore
Forevermore
Bless the Lord, O my soul
O my soul, worship His holy name
Sing like never before, O my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
Bless the Lord, O my soul
O my soul, worship His holy name
Sing like never before, O my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
Yes I will worship Your holy name
Lord, I'll worship Your holy name
Sing like never before, O my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
I will worship Your holy name
Worship Your holy name