In days of peace and days of rest
In times of loss and loneliness
Though rich or poor, Your word is true
That all my ways are known to You
No trial has come beyond Your hand
No step I walk beyond Your plan
The path is dark outside my view
Still all my ways are known to You
And oh what peace that I have found
Wherever I may be
For all my ways are known to You
Hallelujah, they are known to You!
I do not fear the final night
For death will be the door to life
You take my hand and lead me through
For all my ways are known to You
And oh what peace that I have found
Wherever I may be
For all my ways are known to You
Hallelujah, they are known to You!
Open up my eyes so I may see
That You have made these ways for me
That You my God, will walk with me
Open up my eyes so I may see
That You have made these ways for me
That You my God, will walk with me
And oh what peace that I have found
Wherever I may be
For all my ways are known to You
Hallelujah, they are known to You!
And oh what peace that I have found
Wherever I may be
For all my ways are known to You
Hallelujah, they are known to You!