All sufficient merit
Shining like the sun
A fortune I inherit
By no work I have done
My righteousness I forfeit
At my Savior's cross
Where all sufficient merit
Did what I could not
In love He condescended
Eternal now in time
A life without a blemish
The Maker made to die
The law could never save us
Our lawlessness had won
Until the pure and spotless
Lamb had finally come
It is done, it is finished
No more debt I owe
Paid in full
All sufficient merit now my own
I lay down my garments
Any empty boasts
Good works all corrupted
By the sinful host
I'm dressed in my Lord Jesus
A crimson robe made white
No more fear of judgement
His righteousness is mine
It is done, it is finished
No more debt I owe
Paid in full
All sufficient merit now my own
It is done, it is finished
No more debt I owe
Paid in full
All sufficient merit now my own
All sufficient merit
Firm in life and death
The joy of my salvation
Shall be my final breath
And when I stand accepted
Before the throne of God
I'll gaze upon my Jesus
And thank Him for the cross
Yes I'll thank You for the cross
It is done, it is finishe
No more debt I owe
Paid in full
All sufficient merit now my own
It is done, it is finished
No more debt I owe
Paid in full
All sufficient merit now my own
Your Merit now my own