Be thou my vision
O Lord of my heart
Naught be all else to me
Save that thou art
Thou my best thought
By day or by night
Waking or sleeping
Thy presence my light
Be thou my wisdom
And thou my true word
I ever with thee and
Thou with me, Lord
Thou my great father
I thy true son
Thou in me dwelling
And I with thee one
Be thou my battle shield
Sword for my fight
Be thou my dignity
Thou my delight
Thou my soul's shelter
Thou my high tower
Raise me thou heavenward
Oh pow'r of my pow'r
Riches thy heed not
Nor man's empty praise
Thou mine inheiritance
Now and always
Thou and thou only
First in my heart
High king of heaven
My treasure thou art
Thou and thou only
First in my heart
High king of heaven
My treasure thou art