Behold the King has come
Divinity incarnate
Creator of the world
Breathing our air
Behold what light has come
And the dark cannot contain it
The Savior of the world
Is finally here
Oh come let us adore Him
Come let us adore Him
For He alone is worthy
Christ the Lord
Behold, the Father's love
Beyond all comprehension
He gave His only Son
To die in our place
Go and see that empty tomb
He's not there for He is risen
Every heart prepare Him room
Jesus Christ the King of Heaven
Oh come let us adore Him
Come let us adore Him
For He alone is worthy
Christ the Lord
We give You all the glory
We praise Your name
Jesus, we praise Your name forever
Christ the Lord
Oh come let us adore Him
Come let us adore Him
For He alone is worthy
Christ the Lord
Oh come let us adore Him
Come let us come adore Him
For He alone is worthy
Christ the Lord
He is Christ the Lord