Who has held the
Oceans in his hands?
Who has numbered
Every grain of sand?
Kings and nations
Tremble at his voice
All creation rises to rejoice
Behold our God
Seated on his throne
Come, let us adore him
Behold our king
Nothing can compare
Come, let us adore him
Who has given
Counsel to the Lord?
Who can question
Any of his words?
Who can teach
The one who knows all things?
Who can fathom
All his wondrous deeds?
Behold our God
Seated on his throne
Come, let us adore him
Behold our king
Nothing can compare
Come, let us adore him
Who has felt the
Nails upon his hands?
Bearing all the
Guilt of sinful man
God eternal
Humbled to the grave
Jesus, Savior
Risen now to reign
Behold our God
Seated on his throne
Come, let us adore him
Behold our king
Nothing can compare
Come, let us adore him
# Marco'd Greg to ask about this
You will reign forever
(let Your glory fill the Earth)
(let Your glory fill-)
Behold our God
seated on his throne
Come, let us adore him
Behold our king
nothing can compare
Come, let us adore
Behold our God
seated on his throne
Come, let us adore him
Behold our king
nothing can compare
Come, let us adore him