Oh to be
Empty and lowly
Meek and unnoticed
And unknown
And to God, a vessel holy
Filled with Christ
And Christ alone
How great is God!
His grandeur endless
How frail I come
Before His throne
I am lost
In love relentless
That Christ be all
And I His own
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope
Not I, but Christ in me
I am poor
And I have nothing
All my deeds cannot avail
But Christ
endured the Father's crushing
He bowed His head, as Mercy bled,
peace to prevail
He bowed His head, as Mercy bled
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope
Not I, but Christ in me
Bring me low
My heart lower still
That Your grace
My pride relieves
May these words
Resound loud until
Every tribe
And tongue believes
Bring me low
My heart lower still
That Your grace
My pride relieves
May these words
Resound loud until
Every tribe
And tongue can sing
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
May Christ be all
And I be nothing
This is my hope
Not I, but Christ in me
On golden shores
Of sure salvation
I will run to meet my King
Freed from shame
And all accusation
He'll give Himself
Nothing I'll bring