What is our hope in life and death
Christ alone Christ alone
What is our only confidence
That our souls to him belong
Who holds our days within his hand
What comes apart from his command
And what will keep us to the end
The love of Christ in which we stand
O sing hallelujah
Our hope springs eternal
Now and ever we confess
Christ our hope in life and death
What truth can calm the troubled soul
God is good God is good
Where is his grace and goodness known
In our great Redeemer's blood
Who holds our faith when fears arise
Who stands above the stormy trial
Who sends the waves that bring us nigh
Unto the shore, the rock of Christ
O sing hallelujah
Our hope springs eternal
Now and ever we confess
Christ our hope in life and death
Unto the grave what shall we sing
Christ, he lives Christ, he lives
And what reward will heaven bring
Everlasting life with him
There we will rise to meet the Lord
Then sin and death will be destroyed
And we will feast in endless joy
When Christ is ours forevermore
O sing hallelujah
Our hope springs eternal
Now and ever we confess
Christ our hope in life and death
O sing hallelujah
Our hope springs eternal
Now and ever we confess
Christ our hope in life and death
Oh now and ever we confess