Mine are days that
God has numbered
I was made to
walk with Him
Yet I look for
worldly treasure
And forsake the
King of kings
But mine is hope
in my Redeemer
Though I fall
His love is sure
For Christ has paid
for every failing
I am His forevermore
Mine are tears in
times of sorrow
Darkness not
yet understood
Through the valley
I must travel
Where I see no
earthly good
But mine is peace
that flows from Heaven
And the strength
in times of need
I know my pain
will not be wasted
Christ completes
his work in me
Mine are days here
as a stranger
Pilgrim on a
narrow way
One with Christ
I will encounter
Harm and hatred
for His name
But mine is armour
for this battle
Strong enough
to last the war
And He has said
He will deliver
Safely to the
golden shore
And mine are keys
to Zion city
Where beside
the King I walk
For there my heart
has found its treasure
Christ is mine forevermore
Come rejoice now
O my soul
For His love
is my reward
Fear is gone and
hope is sure
Christ is mine forevermore
Come rejoice now
O my soul
For His love
is my reward
Fear is gone and
hope is sure
Christ is mine forevermore
Come rejoice now
O my soul
For His love is my reward
Fear is gone and
hope is sure
Christ is mine forevermore
And mine are keys
to Zion city
Where beside the King I walk
For there my heart has
found its treasure
Christ is mine forevermore