Come behold the wondrous mystery
In the dawning of the king
He the theme of Heaven's praises
Robed in frail humanity
In our longing in our darkness
Now the light of life has come
Look to Christ who condescended
Took on flesh to ransom us
Come behold the wondrous mystery
He is the perfect son of man
In His living in His suffering
Never trace nor stain of sin
See the true and better Adam
Come to save the hell-bound man
Christ the great
and sure fulfilment
Of the law in Him we stand
Come behold the wondrous mystery
Christ the Lord upon the tree
In the stead of ruined sinners
Hangs the lamb in victory
See the price of our redemption
See the Father's plan unfold
Bringing many sons to glory
Grace unmeasured love untold
Come behold the wondrous mystery
Slain by death the God of life
But no grave could
ever restrain Him
Praise the Lord He is alive
What a foretaste of deliverance
How unwavering our hope
Christ in power resurrected
As we will be when He comes
What a foretaste of deliverance
How unwavering our hope
Christ in power resurrected
As we will be when He comes
What a foretaste of deliverance
How unwavering our hope
Christ in power resurrected
As we will be when He comes