Crown Him with many crowns
The lamb upon the throne
Hark! How the heav'nly anthem drowns
All music but its own
Awake my soul and sing
Of Him who died for thee
And hail Him as thy matchless king
Thru all eternity
Crown Him the Son of God
Before the worlds began
And ye who tread where He hath trod
Crown Him the Son of Man
Who every grief hath known
That wrings the human breast
And takes and bears them for His own
That all in Him may rest
Crown Him the Lord of life
Who triumphed o'er the grave
And rose victorious in the strife
For those He came to save
His glories now we sing
Who died and rose on high
Who died eternal life to bring
And lives that death may die
Crown Him the Lord of Heaven
Enthroned in worlds above
Crown Him the King
To Whom Is Given
The Wonderous Name of Love
Crown Him with many crowns
As thrones before Him fall
Crown Him ye kings
With many crowns
For He is King of All