Now the days and hours and moments
Of our suff'ring seem so long
And the toilsome wait and wond'ring
Threaten silence to our song
Now our pain is real and pressing
Where our faith is thin and weak
But our hope is set on Jesus
And we cling to him, our strength
Oh eternal weight of glory!
Oh inheritance divine!
We will see our Lord redeeming
Every past and future time
All our pains will be transfigured
Like the scars of Christ our Lord
We will see the weight of glory
And our broken years restored
For behold! I tell a myst'ry
At the trumpet sound we'll wake
Death is swallowed up in vict'ry!
When we meet our King of Grace
Every year we thought was wasted
Every night we cried "How long?"
All will be a passing moment
In our Savior's vict'ry song
We will see our wounded Savior
We'll behold him face to face
And we'll hear our anguished stories
Sung as vict'ry songs of grace
For behold! I tell a myst'ry
At the trumpet sound we'll wake
Death is swallowed up in vict'ry!
When we meet our King of Grace
Every year we thought was wasted
Every night we cried "How long?"
All will be a passing moment
In our Savior's vict'ry song
Every year we thought was wasted
Every night we cried "How long?"
All will be a passing moment
In our Savior's vict'ry song