Amazing love
That welcomes me
The kindness of mercy
That bought with blood
wholeheartedly
My soul undeserving
God, You're so good
You're so good to me
Behold the cross
Age to age
And hour by hour
The dead are raised
the sinner saved
The work of Your power
God, You're so good
You're so good to me
I am blessed, I am called
I am healed, I am whole
I am saved in Jesus' name
Highly favored, anointed
Filled with Your power
For the glory of Jesus' name
I am blessed, I am called
I am healed, I am whole
I am saved in Jesus' name
Highly favored, anointed
Filled with Your power
For the glory of Jesus' name
And should this life
Bring suffering
Lord, I will remember
What Calvary has bought for me
Both now and forever
And forever
God, You're so good
You're so good to me
I am blessed, I am called
I am healed, I am whole
I am saved in Jesus' name
Highly favored, anointed
Filled with Your power
For the glory of Jesus' name
I am blessed, I am called
I am healed, I am whole
I am saved in Jesus' name
Highly favored, anointed
Filled with Your power
For the glory of Jesus' name
God, You're so good
God, oh You're so good
You're so good to me