God the Uncreated One
The author of salvation
Who wrote the laws of space and time
And fashioned worlds to His design
The One whom angel hosts revere
Hung the stars like chandeliers
Numbered every grain of sand
Knows the heart of every man
He is King forever
He is King forevermore
God our fortress and our strength
The rock on which we can depend
Matchless in His majesty
His power and authority
Unshaken by the schemes of man
Never-changing, Great I Am
Kingdoms rise and kingdoms fall
He is faithful through it all
Crown Him King forever
Crown Him King forevermore
Oh, forevermore
Mighty God in mortal flesh
Forsaken by a traitor's kiss
The curse of sin and centuries
Did pierce the lowly Prince of Peace
Oh, lifted high, the sinless man
Crucified, the spotless Lamb
Buried by the sons of man
He was rescued by the Father's hand
To reign as King forever
Reign as King forever
Reign as King forevermore
King Eternal, God of grace
We crown You with the highest praise
Heaven shouts and saints adore
You're holy, holy, holy Lord!
What joy in everlasting life
All is love and faith is sight
Justice rolls and praises rise
At the name of Jesus Christ
King of kings forever
King of kings forevermore
He is King of kings forever
King of kings forever
King of kings forevermore
Oh, forevermore