I love You Lord
Oh Your mercy never fails me
All my days
I've been held by Your hands
From the moment that I wake up
Until I lay my head
Oh I will sing of the goodness of God
All my life
You have been faithful
You have been so, so good
With every breath that I am able
Oh I will sing
of the goodness of God
I love Your voice
You have led me through the fire
In darkest nights
You are close like no other
I've known You as a father
I've known You as a friend
And I have lived in the goodness of God
All my life
You have been faithful
You have been so, so good
With every breath that I am able
Oh I will sing
of the goodness of God
'Cause Your goodness is running after
it's running after me
Your goodness is running after
With my life laid down
I surrender now
I give You everything
Your goodness is running after
it's running after me
With my life laid down
I surrender now
I give You everything
Your goodness is running after
it's running after me
All my life
You have been faithful
You have been so, so good
With every breath that I am able
Oh I will sing
of the goodness of God
All my life
You have been faithful
You have been so, so good
With every breath that I am able
Oh I will sing
of the goodness of God