I searched the world
But it couldn't fill me
Man's empty praise
And treasures that fade
Are never enough
Then You came along
And put me back together
And every desire is now satisfied
Here in Your love
Oh, there's nothing
Better than You
There's nothing
Lord, there's nothing
Nothing is better than You, no
I'm not afraid
To show You my weakness
My failures and flaws
Lord, You've seen them all
And You still call me friend
'Cause the God of the mountain
Is the God of the valley
And there's not a place
Your mercy and grace
Won't find me again
Oh, there's nothing
Better than You
Lord, there's nothing
Nothing is better than You
Oh, there's nothing
Better than You
Lord, there's nothing
Nothing is better than You
You turn mourning to dancing
You give beauty for ashes
You turn shame into glory
You're the only one who can
You turn mourning to dancing
You give beauty for ashes
You turn shame into glory
You're the only one who can
You turn graves into gardens
You turn bones into armies
You turn seas into highways
You're the only one who can
Oh, there's nothing
Better than You
Lord, there's nothing
Oh, there's nothing
Nothing is better than You
There's nothing
Oh, there's nothing better than You
Better than You
There's nothing
Nothing is better than You
You turn graves into gardens
You turn bones into armies
You turn seas into highways
You're the only one who can