Hark! the herald angels sing
Glory to the newborn King
Peace on earth, and mercy mild
God and sinners reconciled
Joyful, all ye nations, rise
Join the triumph of the skies
With the angelic host proclaim
Christ is born in Bethlehem
Hark! the herald angels sing
Glory to the newborn King
Christ, by highest heav'n adored
Christ, the everlasting Lord
Late in time behold him come
Offspring of a virgin's womb
Veiled in flesh the Godhead see
Hail, the incarnate deity
Pleased as man with man to dwell
Jesus, our Emmanuel
Hark! the herald angels sing
Glory to the newborn King
Hail, the heaven-born
Prince of peace
Hail the Son of righteousness
Light and life to all he brings
Ris'n with healing in his wings
Mild he lays his glory by
Born that man no more may die
Born to raise the suns of earth
Born to give them second birth
Hark! the herald angels sing
Glory to the newborn King