When the music fades
And all is stripped away
And I simply come
Longing just to bring
Something that's of worth
That will bless your heart
I'll bring you more than a song
For a song in itself
Is not what you have required
You search much deeper within
Through the way things appear
You're looking into my heart
I'm coming back to the
Heart of worship
It's all about you
It's all about you, Jesus
I'm sorry Lord for
The thing I've made it
It's all about you
It's all about you, Jesus
King of endless worth
No one could express
How much you deserve
Though I'm weak and poor
All I have is yours
Every single breath
I'll bring you more than a song
For a song in itself
Is not what you have required
You search much deeper within
Through the way things appear
You're looking into my heart
I'm coming back to the
Heart of worship
It's all about you
It's all about you, Jesus
I'm sorry Lord for the
Thing I've made it
It's all about you
It's all about you Lord
I'm coming back to the
Heart of worship
It's all about you
It's all about you, Jesus
I'm sorry Lord for the
Thing I've made it
It's all about you
It's all about you, Jesus
I'll bring you more than a song
More than a song
By your grace, God
I'll bring you more than a song
More than a song
By your grace, God
I'll bring you more than a song
More than a song