Praise the Lord, His mercy is more
Stronger than darkness, new every morn
Our sins they are many, His mercy is more
What love could remember
No wrongs we have done
Omniscient, all knowing
He counts not their sum
Thrown into a sea
Without bottom or shore
Our sins they are many
His mercy is more
Praise the Lord, His mercy is more
Stronger than darkness, new every morn
Our sins they are many, His mercy is more
What patience would wait
As we constantly roam
What Father, so tender
Is calling us home
He welcomes the weakest
The vilest, the poor
Our sins they are many
His mercy is more
Praise the Lord, His mercy is more
Stronger than darkness, new every morn
Our sins they are many, His mercy is more
What riches of kindness
He lavished on us
His blood was the payment
His life was the cost
We stood 'neath a debt
We could never afford
Our sins they are many
His mercy is more
Praise the Lord, His mercy is more
Stronger than darkness, new every morn
Our sins they are many, His mercy is more
Praise the Lord, His mercy is more
Stronger than darkness, new every morn
Our sins they are many, His mercy is more
Our sins they are many, His mercy is mоre