Oh Lord my God
When I in awesome wonder
Consider all the
Worlds Thy hands have made
I see the stars
I hear the rolling thunder
Thy power throughout
The universe displayed
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
And when I think that God
Is Son not sparing
Sent Him to die
I scarce can take it in
That on the cross
My burden gladly bearing
He bled and died
TO take away my sin
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
Then Christ shall come
With shouts of acclamation
And lead me home what joy
Hall fill my heart
Then I shall bow with
Humble adoration
And then proclaim
My God how great Thou art
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art
Then sings my soul
My Saviour God to Thee
How great Thou art