When this life of trials
test my faith
I set my hope on Jesus
When the questions come
and doubts remain
I set my hope on Jesus
For the deepest wounds
that time won't heal
There's a joy that
runs still deeper
There's a truth that's more
than all I feel
I set my hope on Jesus
My rock, my only trust
Who set His heart upon me first
I set my hope on Jesus
Though I falter in this
war with sin
I set my hope on Jesus
When I fail the fight
and sink within
I set my hope on Jesus
Though the shame would
drown me in its sea
And I dread the waves of justice
I will cast my life on Calvary
I set my hope on Jesus
My rock, my only trust
Who set His heart upon me first
I set my hope on Jesus
Though the world called me
to leave my Lord
I set my hope on Jesus
Though it offer all its
vain rewards
I set my hope on Jesus
Though this heart of mine
is prone to stray
Give me grace enough to finish
'Til I worship on that final day
I set my hope on Jesus
My rock, my only trust
Who set His heart upon me first
I set my hope on Jesus
My rock, my only trust
Who set His heart upon me first
I set my hope on Jesus