Lord, from the depths
I call to You
Lord, hear me from on high
And give attention
to my voice
When I for mercy cry
Out of the depths I cry to You
In darkest places I will call
Incline Your ear to me anew
And hear my cry for mercy, Lord
Were You to count my sinful ways
How could I come before Your throne
Yet full forgiveness meets my gaze
I stand redeemed by grace alone
I will wait for You
On Your word, I will rely
Surely wait for You
Till my soul is satisfied
So put your hope in God alone
Take courage in His power to save
Completely and forever won
By Christ emerging from the grave
I will wait for You
On Your word, I will rely
Surely wait for You
Till my soul is satisfied
Now He has come to make a way
And God Himself has paid the price
That all who trust in Him today
Find healing in His sacrifice
I will wait for You
On Your word, I will rely
Surely wait for You
Till my soul is satisfied
I will wait for You
Through the storm and through the night
Surely wait for You
For Your love is my delight
I pray my soul waits for the Lord
My hope is in His word
More than the watchman waits for dawn
My soul waits for the Lord