In Christ alone
my hope is found
He is my light, my strength, my song
This cornerstone
this solid ground
Firm through the fiercest
drought and storm
What heights of love
what depths of peace
When fears are stilled
when strivings cease
My comforter, my all in all
Here in the love of Christ
I stand
In Christ alone
who took on flesh
Fullness of God in helpless babe
This gift of love
and righteousness
Scorned by the ones He came to save
Till on that cross as Jesus died
The wrath of God was satisfied
For every sin on Him was laid
Here in the death of Christ
I live
There in the ground
His body lay
Light of the world
by darkness slain
Then bursting forth
in glorious day
Up from the grave He rose again
And as He stands in victory
Sin's curse has lost
its grip on me
For I am His and He is mine
Bought with the precious
blood of Christ
No guilt in life
no fear in death
This is the power of Christ in me
From life's first cry
to final breath
Jesus commands my destiny
No power of hell
no scheme of man
Can ever pluck me from His hand
Till He returns or calls me home
Here in the power of Christ
I'll stand
No power of hell
no scheme of man
Can ever pluck me from His hand
Till He returns or calls me home
Here in the power of Christ
I'll stand