Do you feel the world is broken
(We do)
Do you feel the shadows deepen
But do you know
That all the dark won't
Stop the light
From getting through
(We do)
Do you wish that you
Could see it all made new
(We do)
Is all creation groaning
(It is)
Is a new creation coming
Is the glory of the Lord
To be the light within our midst
(It is)
Is it good that we
Remind ourselves of this
(It is)
Is anyone worthy
Is anyone whole
Is anyone able to break the seal
And open the scroll
The Lion of Judah
Who conquered the grave
He was David's root
And the Lamb who died to ransom the slave
Is He worthy
Of all blessing and honor and glory
Is He worthy of this
He is
Does the Father truly love us
(He does)
Does the Spirit move among us
And does Jesus our Messiah
Hold forever those He loves
(He does)
Does our God intend to
Dwell again with us
(He does)
Is anyone worthy
Is anyone whole
Is anyone able to
Break the seal and open the scroll
The Lion of Judah
Who conquered the grave
He is David's root
And the Lamb who died
To ransom the slave
From every people and tribe
Every nation and tongue
He has made us a kingdom
And priests to God
To reign with the Son
Is He worthy
Of all blessing and honor and glory
Is He worthy of this
He is
Is He worthy
(Is He worthy)
He is