When peace like a river attendeth my way
When sorrows like sea billows roll
Whatever my lot, Thou hast taught me to say
It is well, it is well with my soul
It is well (it is well)
With my soul (with my soul)
It is well, it is well with my soul
My sin, oh the bliss
Of this glorious thought
My sin, not in part, but the whole
Is nailed to the cross
And I bear it no more
Praise the Lord, praise the Lord oh, my soul
It is well (it is well)
With my soul (with my soul)
It is well, it is well with my soul
And Lord, haste the day
When my faith shall be sight
The cloud be rolled back as a scroll
The trump shall resound
And the Lord shall descend
Even so, it is well with my soul
It is well (it is well)
With my soul (with my soul)
It is well, it is well with my soul
Well with my soul
You're well with my soul