See Him in Jerusalem
Walking where the crowds are
Once these streets had sung to Him
Now they cry for murder
Such a frail and lonely man
Holding up the heavy cross
See Him walking in Jerusalem
On the road to save us
See him there upon the hill
Hear the scorn and laughter
Silent as a lamb he waits
Praying to the father
See the king who made the sun
And the moon and shining stars
Let the soldiers hold and nail him down
So that he could save them
See him there upon the cross
Now no longer breathing
Dust that formed the watching crowds
Takes the blood of Jesus
Feel the earth is shaking now
See the veil is split in two
And he stood before the wrath of God
Shielding sinners with his blood
See the empty tomb today
Death could not contain him
Once the servant of the world
Now in victory reigning
Lift your voices to the one
Who is seated on the throne
See him in the new Jerusalem
Praise the one who saved us
Lift your voices to the one
Who is seated on the throne
See him in the new Jerusalem
Praise the one who saved us