I hear the savior say
Thy strength indeed is small
Child of weakness, watch and pray
Find in me thine all in all
Jesus paid it all
all to him I owe
Sin had left a crimson stain
He washed it white as snow
Lord now indeed I find
Thy power and thine alone
Can change the lepers spots
And melt the heart of stone
Jesus paid it all
All to him I owe
Sin had left a crimson stain
He washed it white as snow
And when before the throne
I stand in him complete
Jesus died my soul to save
My lips shall still repeat
Jesus paid it all
All to him I owe
Sin had left a crimson stain
He washed it white as snow
Oh praise the one who paid my debt
And raises life up from the dead