Joy to the world The Lord is come
Let earth receive Her King
Let ev'ry heart prepare Him room
And Heaven and nature sing
And Heaven and nature sing
And Heav'n
and Heav'n and nature sing
We will sing sing sing
Joy to the world
Joy to the world The Savior reigns
Let men their songs employ
While fields and floods
rocks hills and plains
Repeat the sounding joy
Repeat repeat
the sounding joy
We will sing sing sing
Joy to the world
we will sing sing sing
He rules the world
with truth and grace
And makes the nations prove
The glories of His righteousness
And wonders of His love
And wonders
wonders of His love
We will sing sing sing
Joy to the world
Joyful joyful we adore thee
God of glory Lord of Love
Hearts unfold like flowers before thee
opening to the sun above
Joyful joyful we adore thee
God of glory Lord of Love
Hearts unfold like flowers before thee
opening to the sun above
We will sing sing sing
Joy to the world