Light of the world
Treasure of Heaven
Brilliant like the stars
In the wintery sky
Joy of the Father
Reach through the darkness
Shine across the Earth
Send the shadows to flight
Light of the world
From the beginning
The tragedies of time
Were no match for Your love
From great heights of glory
You saw my story
God, You entered in
And became one of us
Sing hallelujah
For the things He has done
Come and adore Him
Bow down before Him
Sing hallelujah
To the light of the world
Light of the world
Crown in a manger
Born for the cross
To suffer, to save
High King of Heaven
Death is the poorer
We are the richer
By the price that He paid
Sing hallelujah
For the things He has done
Come and adore Him
Bow down before Him
Sing hallelujah
To the light of the world
You're the light of the world
Light up the dark
Light of the world
Soon will be coming
With fire in His eyes
He will ransom His own
Through clouds He will lead us
Straight into glory
And there He shall reign forevermore
Forevermore
Sing hallelujah
For the things He has done
Come and adore Him
Bow down before Him
And sing hallelujah
To the light of the world
The light of the world