Man of sorrows man of God
By his own betrayed
The sin of man and wrath of God
Has been on Jesus lain
Silent as he stood accused
Beaten mocked and scorned
Bowing to the Father's will
He took a crown of thorns
Oh that rugged cross my salvation
Where your love poured out over me
Now my soul cries out Hallelujah
Praise and honour unto thee
Sent of Heaven God's own son
To purchase and redeem
And reconcile the very ones
Who nailed him to that tree
Oh that rugged cross my salvation
Where your love poured out over me
Now my soul cries out Hallelujah
Praise and honour unto thee
Now my debt is paid
It is paid in full
By the precious blood
That my Jesus spilled
Now the curse of sin
Has no hold on me
Whom the son sets free
Oh is free indeed
Now my debt is paid
It is paid in full
By the precious blood
That my Jesus spilled
Now the curse of sin
Has no hold on me
Whom the son sets free
Oh is free indeed
Oh that rugged cross my salvation
Where your love poured out over me
Now my soul cries out Hallelujah
Praise and honour unto thee
See the stone is rolled away
Behold the empty tomb
Hallelujah God be praised
He's risen from the grave
Oh that rugged cross my salvation
Where your love poured out over me
Now my soul cries out Hallelujah
Praise and honour unto thee