Marvelous grace of our
loving Lord
Grace that exceeds
our sin and our guilt
Yonder on Calvary's
mount out-poured
There where the blood
of the Lamb was spilt
Grace grace God's grace
Grace that will pardon
and cleanse within
Grace grace God's grace
Grace that is greater
than all our sin
Sin and despair like
the sea-waves cold
Threaten the soul
with infinite loss
Grace that is greater
yes grace untold
Points to the Refuge
the mighty Cross
Grace grace God's grace
Grace that will pardon
and cleanse within
Grace grace God's grace
Grace that is greater
than all our sin
Marvelous infinite
matchless grace
Freely bestowed
on all who believe
You that are longing
to see His face
Will you this moment
His grace receive
Grace grace God's grace
Grace that will pardon
and cleanse within
Grace grace God's grace
Grace that is greater
than all our sin