My Jesus, I love Thee
I know Thou art mine
For Thee all the follies
of sin I resign
My gracious Redeemer
my Savior art Thou
If ever I loved Thee
my Jesus, 'tis now
I love Thee because
Thou hast first loved me
And purchased my pardon
on Calvary's tree
I love Thee for wearing
the thorns on Thy brow
If ever I loved Thee
my Jesus, 'tis now
I'll love Thee in life
and I will love Thee in death
And praise Thee as long
as Thou lendest me breath
And say when the death
dew lies cold on my brow
If ever I loved Thee
my Jesus, 'tis now
Right now
Redeemer
My Savior
Oh-whoa
'Tis now
Right now
Today's the day
Oh You would love me first
Let the amen sound from his people again
Gladly forever adore him