When the enemy surrounds
And my heart grows faint within
When the darkness overwhelms
And my fears are pressing in
I will trust in You
Oh, Lord
In the silence I will wait
I will stand upon Your word
You're my solid rock
And my salvation
My steadfast hope
That won't be shaken
My soul will wait
For You
You're my stronghold and my shield
In the midst of every threat
Though the wicked never yield
They will vanish like a breath
Yes I know the outcome's sure
Satan's evil plans will fail
In Your power I'm secure
You're my solid rock
And my salvation
My steadfast hope
That won't be shaken
My soul will wait
For You
You're my comfort
When I feel forsaken
My refuge and
My sure foundation
My soul will wait
For You
This is love I can't explain
This is mercy unreserved
Through Your sacrifice so great
I have peace that's undeserved
For the battle has been won
And I fear no shame or loss
Now the sting of death is gone
You're my solid rock
And my salvation
My steadfast hope
That won't be shaken
My soul will wait
For You
You're my comfort
When I feel forsaken
My refuge and
My sure foundation
My soul will wait
For You
Pouring out our
Hearts before You
We will trust in You
Perfect Savior
Strong defender
We will trust in You
Pouring out our
Hearts before You
We will trust in You
Perfect Savior
Strong defender
We will trust in You