Oh holy Night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night
Of our dear Savior's birth
Long lay the world
In sin and error pining
'Til He appeared
And the soul felt its worth
A thrill of hope
The weary world rejoices
For yonder breaks
A new and glorious morn
Fall on your knees
Oh hear the angel voices
Oh night divine
Oh night, when Christ was born
Oh nigh
Oh night divine
Truly, He taught us
To love one another
His law is love
And His gospel is peace
Chains shall He break
For the slave is our brother
And in His name
All oppression shall cеase
Sweet hymns of joy
In grateful chorus raise wе
Let all within us
Praise His holy name
Christ is the Lord
Oh praise His name forever
His power and glory
Evermore proclaim
Oh night divine
Oh night
Fall on your knees
Oh hear the angel voices
Oh night divine
Oh night, when Christ was born
Oh night
Oh night divine