Who else commands
All the hosts of heaven?
Who else could make
Every king bow down?
Who else can whisper
And darkness trembles?
Only a Holy God
What other beauty
Demands such praises?
What other splendour
Outshines the sun?
What other majesty
Rules with justice?
Only a Holy God
Come and behold Him
The One and the Only
Cry out, sing holy
Forever a Holy God
Come and worship the Holy God
What other glory
Consumes like fire?
What other power
Can raise the dead?
What other name
Remains undefeated?
Only a Holy God
Come and behold Him
The One and the Only
Cry out, sing holy
Forever a Holy God
Come and worship the Holy God
Come and behold Him
The One and the Only
Cry out, sing holy
Forever a Holy God
Come and worship the Holy God
Who else could rescue
Me from my failing?
Who else would offer
His only Son?
Who else invites me
To call Him Father?
Only a Holy God
Only my Holy God
Come and behold Him
The One and the Only
Cry out, sing holy
Forever a Holy God
Come and worship the Holy God
Come and behold Him
The One and the Only
Cry out, sing holy
Forever a Holy God
Come and worship the Holy God
Come and behold Him
The One and the Only
Cry out, sing holy
Forever a Holy God
Come and worship the Holy God