Oh, to see the dawn
of the darkest day
Christ on the road to Calvary
Tried by sinful men
torn and beaten, then
Nailed to a cross of wood
This, the power of the cross
Christ became sin for us
Took the blame, bore the wrath
We stand forgiven at the cross
Oh, to see the pain
written on Your face
Bearing the awesome
weight of sin
Ev'ry bitter thought
ev'ry evil deed
Crowning Your bloodstained brow
This, the power of the cross
Christ became sin for us
Took the blame, bore the wrath
We stand forgiven at the cross
Now the daylight flees
now the ground beneath
Quakes as its Maker bows His head
Curtain torn in two
dead are raised to life
Finished the vict'ry cry
Oh, to see my name
written in the wounds
For through Your suffering I am free
Death is crushed to death
life is mine to live
Won through Your selfless love
This, the power of the cross
Christ became sin for us
Took the blame, bore the wrath
We stand forgiven at the cross
Oh, to see my name
written in the wounds
For through Your suffering I am free
Death is crushed to death
life is mine to live
Won through Your selfless love
This, the power of the cross
Son of God, slain for us
What a love, what a cost
We stand forgiven at the cross
This, the power of the cross
Son of God, slain for us
What a love, what a cost
We stand forgiven at the cross