Praise to the Lord
the Almighty
the King of creation!
O my soul praise Him
for He is thy
health and salvation!
All ye who hear
now to His temple draw near,
Praise Him in glad adoration.
Praise to the Lord
who o’er all things
so wondrously reigneth
Shelters thee under
His wings yea
so gently sustaineth!
Hast thou not seen
how thy desires e’er have been
Granted in what He ordaineth?
Halleluja
Praise to the Lord
who doth prosper
thy work and defend thee!
Surely His goodness
and mercy
here daily attend thee
Ponder anew
what the Almighty can do
If with His love He befriend thee
Praise to the Lord
O let all that
is in me adore Him!
All that hath life and breath
come now with praises before Him!
Let the amen
sound from His people again
Gladly forever adore Him
Let the amen
sound from His people again
Gladly forever adore Him
Halleluja