Rejoice in the Lord
now and always
Sing it again
we rejoice
Delight in the love
He has shown us
Gratefully lift
up your voice
His gentleness among us
Will join our hearts with praise
We gather in His goodness
A family of grace
With each breath He's given
praise the Lord
In these times we live in
we will praise the Lord
Throughout every season
I am sure
We have every reason
to praise the Lord
Rejoice and be
anxious for nothing
Praying for all
that you need
Come with a song
of thanksgiving
And lay your requests
at His feet
His peace will fall upon us
To guard our hearts and minds
In Christ who reigns eternal
The shepherd of our lives
With each breath He's given
praise the Lord
In these times we live in
we will praise the Lord
Throughout every season
I am sure
We have every reason
to praise the Lord
Rejoice in the Lord
now and always
Tell of the good
He has done
Worship the Lord
to remember
All of the joy
yet to come
The hope that
burns within us
The dark cannot destroy
With praise
that's never-ending
We say again
Rejoice
With each breath He's given
praise the Lord
In these times we live in
we will praise the Lord
Throughout every season
I am sure
We have every reason
to praise the Lord