This kind of thing shouldn't happen to me
I'm just a boy who watches the sheep
But I saw a miracle
A star like the morning lit up the night
A choir of angels filled up the sky
They sang of a miracle
Glory to God in the highest
Peace to His people here on earth
For the Savior is born
Emmanuel God is with us
And He will reign forevermore
Jesus Christ the Lord of Lords
So I ran to that town to see if it's true
Is He really here Had Heaven come through
And oh it was beautiful
Cause there in the stable asleep in her arms
The Lion of Judah the King of my heart
With tears filling up my eyes
Of this I will testify
Glory to God in the highest
Peace to His people here on earth
For the Savior is born
Emmanuel God is with us
And He will reign forevermore
Jesus Christ the Lord of Lords
He brings joy to the world
Joy to the world
Glory to God in the highest
Peace to His people here on earth
For the Savior is born
Emmanuel God is with us
And He will reign forevermore
Jesus Christ the Lord of Lords