Silent night holy night
All is calm all is bright
Round yon virgin mother and child
Holy infant so tender and mild
Sleep in heavenly peace
Silent night holy night
Shepherds quake at the sight
Glories stream from heaven afar
Heavenly hosts sing alleluia
Christ the Savior is born
Holy holy
Hope in a manger for you and for me
Bow down and worship
Come rest your eyes on the King
Jesus our heavenly peace
Silent night holy night
Son of God love's pure light
Radiant beams from thy holy face
With the dawn of redeeming grace
Jesus Lord at thy birth
Holy holy
Hope in a manger for you and for me
Bow down and worship
Come rest your eyes on the King
Jesus our heavenly peace