Speak, O Lord
as we come to You
To receive the food
of Your Holy Word
Take Your truth
plant it deep in us
Shape and fashion us
in Your likeness
That the light of Christ
might be seen today
In our acts of love
and our deeds of faith
Speak, O Lord
and fulfill in us
All Your purposes
for Your glory
Teach us Lord
full obedience
Holy reverence
true humility
Test our thoughts
and our attitudes
In the radiance
of Your purity
Cause our faith to rise
cause our eyes to see
Your majestic love
and authority
Words of pow'r
that can never fail
Let their truth prevail
over unbelief
Speak, O Lord
and renew our minds
Help us grasp the heights
of Your plans for us
Truths unchanged
from the dawn of time
That will echo down
through eternity
And by grace we'll stand
on Your promises
And by faith we'll walk
as You walk with us
Speak, O Lord
till Your church is built
And the earth is filled
with Your glory