There is one Gospel
On which I stand
For all eternity
It is my story
My Father's plan
The Son has rescued me
Oh what a Gospel
Oh what a peace
My highest joy
And my deepest need
Now and forever
He is my light
I stand in the
Gospel of Jesus Christ
There is one Gospel
To which I cling
All else I count as loss
For there
Where justice and mercy meet
He saved me on the cross
No more I boast in
What I can bring
No more I carry
The weight of sin
For He has brought me
From death to life
I stand in the
Gospel of Jesus Christ
There is one Gospel
Where hope is found
The empty tomb still speaks
For death could not
Keep my Saviour down
He lives and I am free
Now on my Saviour
I fix my eyes
My life is His
And His hope is mine
For He has promised
I, too, will rise
I stand in the
Gospel of Jesus Christ
And in this Gospel
The church is one
We do not walk alone
We have His Spirit
As we press on
To lead us safely home
And when in glory
Still I will sing
Of this old story
That rescued me
Praise to my Saviour
The King of life
I stand in the
Gospel of Jesus Christ
And when in glory
Still I will sing
Of this old story
That rescued me
Praise to my Saviour
The King of life
I stand in the
Gospel of Jesus Christ
Praise to my Saviour
The King of life
I stand in the
Gospel of Jesus Christ