Tis so sweet to trust in Jesus
Just to take him at his word
Just to rest upon his promise
And to know thus says the Lord
Jesus Jesus how I trust him
How I've proved him o'er and o'er
Jesus Jesus mighty Jesus
O for grace to trust him more
Tis so sweet
O how sweet to trust in Jesus
Just to trust his priceless blood
And in simple faith to wash me
In the healing cleansing flood
Jesus Jesus how I trust him
How I've proved him o'er and o'er
Jesus Jesus mighty Jesus
O for grace to trust him more
Tis so sweet
Yes tis sweet to trust in Jesus
From the chains of self he frees
Rest in Jesus trade your burdens
For him comfort joy and peace
Jesus Jesus how I trust him
How I've proved him o'er and o'er
Jesus Jesus mighty Jesus
O for grace to trust him more
To trust him more
Tis so sweet