Who is this, divine and tender
Hailing from eternal shores?
Once arrayed in highest splendor
Now in poverty adorned
He is Jesus, God made mortal
Word in flesh, the Light of Life
From a throne room to a stable
Hope is born this holy night
Who is this of might and meekness
Given all authority?
With a word He stills the tempest
At His touch the blind can see
He is Jesus our Messiah
Long awaited, long proclaimed
Sing "Hosanna in the highest!"
Christ the King has come to reign
Who is this reviled and stricken
Broken on a cursed tree?
Son of God by God forsaken
Drenched in our iniquity
He is Jesus slain for sinners
Laiden with our guilt and grief
All our praise to Him we render
For His wounds have won our peace
For You've won our peace
Who is this entombed in darkness
Cast into the bitter depths?
He whom grave nor Hell could harness
Rose and tore the sting from death
He is Jesus, God triumphant
Risen to the Father's side
All will bow in awe and reverence
At the name of Jesus Christ
He is Jesus, God triumphant
Risen to the Father's side
All will bow in awe and reverence
At the name of Jesus Christ
O come let us adore Him
Christ the Lord