What gift of grace
Is Jesus my redeemer
There is no more
For heaven now to give
He is my joy
My righteousness, and freedom
My steadfast love
My deep and boundless peace
To this I hold
My hope is only Jesus
For my life is wholly bound to His
Oh how strange and divine
I can sing, "All is mine"
Yet not I, but through Christ in me
The night is dark
But I am not forsaken
For by my side
The Saviour He will stay
I labour on
In weakness and rejoicing
For in my need
His power is displayed
To this I hold
My Shepherd will defend me
Through the deepest valley
He will lead
Oh the night has been won
And I shall overcome
Yet not I, but through Christ in me
No fate I dread
I know I am forgiven
The future sure
The price it has been paid
For Jesus bled
And suffered for my pardon
And He was raised
To overthrow the grave
To this I hold
My sin has been defeated
Jesus now and ever is my plea
Oh the chains are released
I can sing, "I am free"
Yet not I, but through Christ in me
With every breath
I long to follow Jesus
For He has said
That He will bring me home
And day by day
I know He will renew me
Until I stand
With joy before the throne
To this I hold
My hope is only Jesus
All the glory evermore to Him
When the race is complete
Still my lips shall repeat
Yet not I, but through Christ in me
To this I hold
My hope is only Jesus
All the glory evermore to Him
When the race is complete
Still my lips shall repeat
Yet not I, but through Christ in me
When the race is complete
Still my lips shall repeat
Yet not I, but through Christ in me