I was alone
I couldn't find my place
'Til Heaven reached down
Your love it called my name
Out of my shame
Out of the dead of night
Into a hope
into Your marvelous light
It's Your mercy
I don't deserve Your mercy
That You would reach down for me
and keep me as Your own
For Your glory
I'm living for Your glory
And I will tell the story
of Your unfailing love
Be glorified
Be lifted high
In all my life
Be glorified
Though I may run
Though I may fall apart
Chasing this world
Things that will break Your heart
But faithful and true
Sure as the rising sun
One thing is true
One thing is sure to come
It's Your mercy
I don't deserve Your mercy
That You would reach down for me
And keep me as Your own
For Your glory
I'm living for Your glory
And I will tell the story
of Your unfailing love
Be glorified
be lifted high
In all my life
be glorified
Be glorified
be lifted high
In all my life
be glorified
Be glorified
Oh, I've tasted and seen
that You are good
And You're walking with me
just like You said You would
And all that You say
every word is true
Oh, whom should I trust?
Jesus, I trust in You
Oh, I've tasted and seen
that You are good
And You're walking with me
just like You said You would
And all that You say
every word is true
Oh, whom should I trust?
Jesus, I trust in You
Be glorified
be lifted high
In all my life
be glorified
Be glorified
be lifted high
In all my life
be glorified
Be glorified
It's Your mercy
I don't deserve Your mercy
That You would reach down for
me and keep me as Your own
For Your glory
I'm living for Your glory
And I will tell the story
of Your unfailing love
Your unfailing love