All of creation
All of the earth
Make straight a highway
A path for the Lord
Jesus is coming soon
Call back the sinner
Wake up the saint
Let every nation shout of Your fame
Jesus is coming soon
Like a bride waiting for her groom
We'll be at Church ready for You
Every heart longing for our King
We sing
Even so come
Lord Jesus, come
There will be justice
all will be new
Your name forever
faithful and true
Jesus is coming soon
Oh, like a bride waiting for her groom
We'll be at Church ready for You
Every heart longing for our King
We sing
Even so come
Lord Jesus, come
So we wait
We wait for You
God, we wait
You're coming soon
So we wait
We wait for You
God, we wait
You're coming soon
Like a bride waiting for her groom
We'll be at Church, ready for You
Every heart longing for our King
We sing
Like a bride waiting for her groom
We'll be at Church, we'll be ready for You
Every heart longing for our King
We sing
Even so come
Lord Jesus, come