The dark tried to hide You
And steal You away
Death tried to keep You
Inside of the grave
The enemy fought You
He tried but he lost
You cannot be stopped
When we cried for freedom
You tore down the walls
The weight of our burdens
You carried it all
Our fears and our failures
Hang dead on the cross
You cannot be stopped
Mover of mountains
Breaker of chains
Jesus has triumphed
over the grave
Sing hallelujah
The battle is won
Nothing can stand
against our God
We stand on Your victory
And shout out Your praise
Miracle maker
You're mighty to save
Awesome in power
Relentless in love
You cannot be stopped
Mover of mountains
Breaker of chains
Jesus has triumphed
over the grave
Sing hallelujah
The battle is won
Nothing can stand
against our God
There's nothing
that can stop our God
There is nothing
There's nothing
that can stop our God
There is nothing
There's nothing
that can stop our God
There is nothing
Mover of mountains
Breaker of chains
Jesus has triumphed
over the grave
Sing hallelujah
The battle is won
Nothing can stand
against our God
Sing hallelujah
The battle is won
Nothing can stand
against our God