Oh to be, empty and lowly
Meek and unnoticed, and unknown
And to God, a vessel holy
Filled with Christ, and Christ alone
How great is God! His grandeur endless
How frail I come, before His throne
I am lost, in love relentless
That Christ be all, and I His own
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope: Not I, but Christ in me
I am poor, and I have nothing
All my deeds cannot avail
But Christ endured the Father's crushing
He bowed His head, as Mercy bled,
peace to prevail
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope: Not I, but Christ in me
Bring me low, my heart lower still
That Your grace my pride relieves
May these words resound loud until
Every tribe and tongue believes
Bring me low, my heart lower still
That Your grace my pride relieves
May these words resound loud until
Every tribe and tongue can sing
May Christ be all, and I be nothing
His glory shines in vessels weak
This is my hope: Not I, but Christ in me
On golden shores of sure salvation
I will run to meet my King
Freed from shame and all accusation
He'll give Himself, nothing I'll bring